4 seconds.
That's how long tourists stay
before turning away.
What is this dish?
Is the price fair?
Can I eat this?
How do I order?
Papago translates.
Nothing tells you what to do.
DON'T READ.
JUST ORDER WHAT'S GREEN.
One photo. Three colors:
green · yellow · red.
Tap green — your phone speaks Korean.
Show it to the staff.
Saw a dish online?
Same MenuLens app.
Find 5 restaurants serving it.
20 million tourists in 2026.
41.8% of menus are mistranslated.
₩300M lawsuit at Gwangjang Market.
TourAPI 4.0 + 5 public datasets.
First LOD SPARQL use
in 13 years of the competition.
bestMenu inverted into
a dish ↔ restaurant index.
menulens-app.vercel.app
One tap. Order what's green.